[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e83449fde65bf6ef1fe7a"
  },
  "question": "Bigha and Guintha are",
  "answers": [
    "the type of village house",
    "the type of hybrid seeds",
    "the measuring units of grain",
    "the measuring units of land area in village"
  ],
  "answer": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e84129fde65bf6ef1fe7b"
  },
  "question": "Finance raised to operate a business is called",
  "answers": [
    "labour",
    "enterprise",
    "land",
    "capital"
  ],
  "answer": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e89479fde65bf6ef1fe7c"
  },
  "question": "Minimum wages for a farm labourer set by the government is",
  "answers": [
    "Rupees 80",
    "Rupees 90",
    "Rupees 115",
    "Rupees 120"
  ],
  "answer": 2
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e89559fde65bf6ef1fe7d"
  },
  "question": "The Green Revolution introduced the farmers to",
  "answers": [
    "cultivation of wheat and rice",
    "cultivation of green vegetables",
    "cultivation of sugar cane",
    "cultivation of forests"
  ],
  "answer": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8cc69fde65bf6ef1fe7e"
  },
  "question": "The small farmers constitute about _________ per cent of total farmers in India",
  "answers": [
    "50",
    "60",
    "70",
    "80"
  ],
  "answer": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8cc89fde65bf6ef1fe7f"
  },
  "question": "The new ways of farming need",
  "answers": [
    "less land",
    "more capital",
    "machinery",
    "all of the above"
  ],
  "answer": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8cca9fde65bf6ef1fe80"
  },
  "question": "The most abundant factor of production is",
  "answers": [
    "labour",
    "land",
    "machinery",
    "all of the above"
  ],
  "answer": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8ccc9fde65bf6ef1fe81"
  },
  "question": "Multiple Cropping refers to :",
  "answers": [
    "Cultivation of wheat and rice",
    "cultivation of two crops in alternate rows",
    "cultivating more than one crop on the same field each year",
    "cultivating crops and rearing animals on the same farm"
  ],
  "answer": 2
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8cd09fde65bf6ef1fe82"
  },
  "question": "Working capital stands for :",
  "answers": [
    "Tools, machines and buildings",
    "raw materials and money in hand",
    "total share capital",
    "fixed deposits in financial institutions"
  ],
  "answer": 1
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "611e8cd29fde65bf6ef1fe83"
  },
  "question": "Which one of the following is not an effect of the modern farming?",
  "answers": [
    "Soil degradation",
    "Deforestation",
    "Decrease in groundwater",
    "Water pollution"
  ],
  "answer": 3
}]